Hey, partner!
How's it crack-a-lacking for you on this fine Friday?
Are you ready for some more binding of Isaac?
Hey!
Friday POG!
Hell yeah.
Friday never gets old, man.
Even for me right now, when the days kinda look the same.
There's still something special about Friday.
One sec.
Okay, I'm back.
Thanks for making the bad thoughts go away.
That's what I'm here for, man, among other things.
Mainly, it's, you know, to play video games and have fun with that.
But I'm glad I'm making your bad thoughts go away.
You've found your sack already?
That's good to hear.
Trying Milka's Brownies for the first time and they're horrible.
I've never tried them.
Thanks for warning me.
What, they don't taste like brownies or...?
Friday is the best day, for sure.
That is for sure.
How many Isics are you gonna blind today?
Or bind?
Probably at least two.
We gotta get that Wind Street going, man.
I'm not sure what we'll be doing today.
Maybe challenges and some more normal runs.
Any ideas what you'll be streaming next?
Actually, yes.
I was thinking either The Sims 4 or Hitman World of Assassination.
I don't know what it is about those two games, but I was thinking about those two games.
So maybe one of those.
I don't know why I just got the itch to try something like that.
But don't take my word on this.
This is just me thinking out loud right now.
It could be something completely off the chain, something very different.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
I just got the... I was thinking about Sims.
Like, I loved Sims 1 and Sims 2.
And I haven't played that since I was a kid, you know?
Could be fun to try out.
The only thing that's holding me back a little bit is that The Sims 4 has like a million DLC.
I checked it out on Steam.
What the fuck is going on with the DLC situation of Sims?
That shit is crazy!
Like, what the heck, man?
That is like pure nightmare fuel.
Mega-transactions, exactly.
I feel like there's definitely, if Charlie ever makes a video about The Sims, the title will be The Sims Situation is out of control or something like that.
Hey, what's up, SirD Ryan?
First time catching a stream, watching Minecraft season 1 and 2 since five months.
Nice.
Good to hear.
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
Welcome.
I'm saving Doki Doki for Halloween.
I'm not saving it for anything.
Maybe that's what I'm playing next.
You don't know.
You're never gonna know.
But I was thinking of having some game next to Isaac.
We could play at the same time, you know?
So like on one side, I play a game with the mouse and then with the keyboard we go Isaac.
So it's like multitasking.
We're gonna raise a kid in Sims while we find her sex, you know?
What do you think?
How would streams for The Sims go?
You just like do the live sim or would... I guess I would just play the game, Frank.
I don't really know what Sims is about nowadays.
I'm assuming it's the same as it was back then with The Sims 1 and 2.
I would make a character called Oliver, most likely.
And I would probably try to become an astronaut like I did back then.
And then just play the game, you know?
And make my house and go to work.
Maybe try and find a girlfriend.
I don't know what you... whatever you do in life, right?
Yeah.
That's what I would do.
I would do some some shopping, you know?
And do some...
what do you call it?
Interior decorating?
Yeah.
Become a streamer?
Is that actually a thing in the modern Sims?
It wouldn't surprise me, honestly.
There's probably a streamer pack you can buy.
That's hilarious.
I should stream myself simulating becoming a streamer.
That's so dumb.
I did play The Witness.
Not all of it, though.
I'm missing, like, I think the very end.
It got a little difficult towards the end.
Couldn't quite figure it out.
Yeah, there's so many games to play.
Honestly, like, this backlog that I currently have is hopeless.
I don't think I will ever get through it all.
At least not in a way where I will enjoy it fully, you know?
It's gonna be... if I ever, like, truly intend to go through the entire backlog before I die, it'll become factory-style, and I hate that.
I don't want to just crank things out on a... on one of those collecting bands, you know?
That's a word for that.
A character called About Oliver.
Man, I hate that so much, Diego.
I hate that name.
I wish I could change my name to Oliver David, but someone already took that nickname.
And now, you know, everyone's... it's already so deeply embedded in this whole thing now.
I can't change it.
I hate my YouTube name.
So, when you playing Final Fantasy 15... what up?
Or 14?
How about Final Fantasy 1 and 2 and 3 and 4 and 5 and 6 and 7 and 8 and 9?
What about all the others?
Someone at the other time was like, why don't you play Final Fantasy 9?
Like, I don't even know what Final Fantasy is!
Like, why should I play 9 and 15 and 14 and fucking... let me play it in order, I guess.
There you go, right?
And someone's like, Final Fantasy 7 is the best.
That series blows my mind.
I don't know what's happening with that series.
Why there's so many games.
They can't be good if there's that many iterations of it.
It's got to be slob at some point, no?
Am I... is that just me?
Like, people are saying Call of Duty is, like, slobified because there's, like, eight Call of Duties and there's 15 Final Fantasies?
I mean, if they crank them out that fast,
I don't know what I'm talking about, guys.
I don't know anything about Final Fantasy, okay?
I'm just pulling stuff out of my ass.
Why is it called Final Fantasy if it's not really the final one?
Exactly!
What about Initial Fantasy?
Halfway Fantasy, you know?
You could not imagine me playing Sims?
Why not?
I love The Sims as a kid.
I used to play it with my mom as well.
That was the only game she ever played, actually.
And she was good at it, too.
Recurring Fantasy, I like that one.
Sexual Fantasy.
It's an anthology.
Each entry is completely disconnected but are linked through some elements.
Kind of like patches from FromSoft games.
Ah, I thought you meant, like, patches as in updates at first, but now I see.
I get it.
LoveFromGrease, what's your notes program called?
It's called Pure Ref.
I'm gonna write it in chat.
That's the one I used to make notes where I copy-paste screenshots inside of there and all that.
Yeah, it's really good for that.
It's the one I used for blueprints as well.
It's a great success, by the way.
I don't know what it would have done in that game, if not for this program.
Favorite sexual fantasy?
I don't know.
Probably playing games for a living.
So I'm living it right now.
I'm living that fantasy.
I don't know about sexual, just fantasy.
Wait, what happened?
My whole fucking screen just turned off.
Whoa, I don't know what just happened.
Okay, I'm back.
What the?
I thought I just crashed everything.
I think we're good.
Where are you guys?
I don't even know where the chat is now.
There you are.
Everything just sort of collapsed.
Weird.
Okay, um, let's see.
I think it's time we start playing.
Let me transition.
Also, check this out.
There's a house in the preview now.
That's different.
Man, there's so many mysteries in this game.
Let me see.
Oh yeah, we have this, of course.
Like what's up with all these freaking locked characters?
It's funny, like there's doors here.
Maybe it's like related to me finding the the red door, you know, and you gotta find doors for all of these.
Like for this guy, a polyon, you gotta find a door with a spiral inside.
And for Bethany, you gotta find, well, the upside down, cross, whatever.
Random.
Some kind of eye sack.
Magdalene, I don't know what that's about.
That's like a bunny peeking out of a door.
Cane's door is just straight up locked.
Judas, I don't know what's happening there.
There's a poop inside of that door.
And the night sky is there.
Doesn't this kind of look like that meme with the reaper going from door to door?
You know, where there's blood coming out of the door?
What kind of look like those doors, no?
I'm not sure what to do here.
Like I...
My theory is that when you unlock Lazarus, or this version of Lazarus, you gotta play Lazarus.
Because I played a sasle and I unlocked the sasle, right?
So I think I just gotta play like characters and see what happens.
Could also do challenges.
What's the next one?
Computer savvy.
You know what?
Let's start with a challenge.
Computer savvy.
Let's see what that's all about.
Okay.
Oh, I gotta move this.
God, my mousepad is annoying.
There we go.
Oh, this looks interesting.
Technology!
Okay.
And technology too.
How's that gonna work though?
Wait, they're homing?
But how does that work?
No.
This is broken.
This is gonna be easy.
Are you kidding me?
It's a challenge?
Where's the challenge in this?
Now I just need spectral tears and I'm gonna slap everything.
Okay, I will say though, my damage is not great.
Like the damage stat.
My damage is fine, but my damage stat is bad.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
Easy.
Ewas?
Yeah!
Not bad.
Let's look for floor decoration.
This one.
Beautiful.
Money!
Okay, not bad.
Oh, wait a minute.
Look in the left beneath my keys.
There's a treasure trophy thing with a cross over it or a red line.
I wonder if that's the icon that's telling you, hey, there's no treasure rooms.
Is that actually what that is?
Probably, right?
Also, I'm not sure if I should be clearing everything here, but I'm gonna do it.
Bro, this is really good.
I need to find this in a natural run, man.
I need technology.
Pokego.
I think... Ooh!
I'm rich!
Well, in that case, let me see.
Chance at the start of each new room to summon a permanently charmed monster.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, yeah.
I'll take it.
We're also gonna take a buffer for the next floor, you know, naturally.
A phone tooth appears?
What the... What was that just now?
What does that even mean?
Uh-oh, I'm scared.
Something's wrong.
Ah, well.
I knew the risks.
I think I knew what happened just now.
I spawned this guy, and that's what the phone tooth was about.
I don't know why they would call it that.
Uh, button.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
We could look for secrets, though.
I predict on the left here, but let's see.
That could be.
Never mind.
I'm gonna try one more time.
I think over here.
Yes.
Wonderful.
I've gotten so much money on the first floor.
Let's leave.
Or, I mean, kill the boss and then leave.
Here we go.
It's a hitless horseman.
Oh, no, I got hit.
My buffer for the next floor is in danger.
No, I lost my buffer.
Bro,
this is crazy.
A pony.
Dude, that is pretty damn good.
That's really good.
Nice.
Cheers.
You know what?
Challenges are kind of funny, because every time I think about challenges, I'm like, nah, I don't know.
Fine, I guess I'll do a challenge.
And then whenever I get into a challenge, like, fuck yeah, I love challenges.
I don't know why I don't think like that all the time.
I keep forgetting how fun it is.
Bombs.
Oh, I can fly.
Damn, I should have used my key on this instead.
Okay, well.
Oh, god.
Okay, okay, okay.
You gotta be careful now.
I cannot take damage.
We're going for... let's go for angels.
I like it.
Oh, I need spectral tears, man.
That's gonna save this run.
No tinted rocks.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I would love to take the buffer, but...
Oh, man, the PhD.
I may have to take the PhD instead.
Yeah.
Also, I think there's a secret right here.
You know what?
I'm actually so sure about it.
Let's do it.
Fuck, okay, okay, fine.
Nice.
Another key.
That means we can enter the room.
Dude, technology is out of control.
Spectral tears is what we need.
I think I'm gonna do this.
Also, I need to rem...
How do I use this item again?
I can't use it right now.
I don't... I want to save it.
That's across the screen.
Invulnerable right.
Okay, okay, fine.
Here we go.
Wish me luck.
Duke of Flies should be fine.
Oh, yeah, man.
The technology is gonna wreck this.
Is this the easiest boss of all time with this or what?
Oh, that's nice.
You know what?
I may actually go in.
Do I go for devils?
Nah, you know what?
Here's the thing.
I don't really want anything specific from the devils.
Like Brimstone?
I don't care.
I have a great attack already, right?
We're gonna save for angels.
I'm so proud of myself for realizing that just now.
That was a good reasoning.
Okay.
Well, I'm rich.
Could go in there now since we don't really need to maintain...
Also, wait a minute.
I have like five damage.
I guess the synth oil really helped.
So, here's the thing though.
If I go in here now, will I lose my angel?
Because we already did the floor, right?
I need to test this.
Oh, but wait!
I can dash through the door!
Sick.
Yeah!
Well, I guess I didn't get to test it, but that's okay.
Let's find a secret room.
I think right here.
Okay, maybe here.
Yes.
Okay.
Blow this guy up.
We get angel.
Lovely.
It's not a lot, but you know, maybe that's exactly what we need.
I think I'm ready.
And now we lost all the angel chance.
Why?
I guess we're gonna get it back now, right?
That's how that works.
Kind of weird.
Okay.
Yeah, we got it back.
Who dodged that?
Oh, I forgot to buy the buffer!
Whoops.
Judgment.
I also forgot to buy the freaking PhD.
God damn, son.
That's painful.
I had the money for it and everything.
Whoa!
Hey!
Amazing.
Oh yeah.
Show me the map.
I mean, this is gonna be so easy.
Am I crazy?
Like, where's the challenge here?
I think just the normal mode of the game is way more challenging.
Buttons.
Gym.
Ah!
Damn it.
Blow them up.
And we gain two.
Okay, it's consistent.
A little bit more angel there.
A pill.
Honestly, I don't think that matters for me.
Shot speed is useless.
Jira.
Oh, nice.
We're gonna save that for a rainy day.
Dude, my companion here is doing good damage.
Yeah, go in here.
No, I don't have a key!
Oh, we gotta find one.
No, I got hit!
Yikes.
I think that was actually a good item to take, simply because I don't have any keys.
Dude, I can't get into the shop.
You gotta be kidding me.
No,
that's crazy, man.
I got the money for... Wow, the companion!
Crazy damage.
I mean, okay.
Moving on, I guess.
At this point, I don't really need some In-Max.
I feel like I've already got this one in the bag.
What's that?
The sun!
I'm actually gonna use it, just to reveal the map.
Okay, I guess we want to turn left, yeah.
That's fun.
Oh, god.
Nice.
Dude, this companion right here is gonna carry me.
Got a key.
Ooh, mom's key.
I think that's very much required.
Can you get a buffer?
Yes, sir.
And we can even refresh.
Another buffer.
Okay, I'll blow you up as well.
That also gave me... Oh my god, dude.
I can get this if I wanted to, but I don't want to.
Full health.
Humbling bundle.
That could be pretty good, I guess.
But it is a little late in the run for that.
Shit.
Oh wait, I should have used Jera in the shop!
Dang, I could have... yeah.
I'll save it for an even rainier day.
How about that?
Wow.
Angels!
All right, you're dead, son.
Wait, I should have used Jera!
Prime opportunity for Jera!
I got too excited, guys!
No!
Oh my god.
I'm so sorry to myself, to all of you, mostly to myself.
That is crazy.
You know what?
That would have made things too easy, right?
You gotta keep it interesting.
Yeah, that would have just made it way too easy.
We're already on such a roll here, you know?
We gotta calm down a bit.
Thank you.
Nice.
Oh my god!
Okay, I'll take that.
That's nice.
Some of that potential health I didn't take before I now have.
Oh my god, really?
Special tears, I need it!
Why is this challenge run so easy?
I feel like they shouldn't have been called challenge, more like scenarios.
Watch the scenario.
Holy fucker!
Feels like I'm playing a sasle.
Dude, I'm going in here.
Sick.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
All right, I think we're ready to leave.
11 coins?
We could maybe go back to the shop and buy something else.
Now I look at my HP and all that, I think it was a good choice to save the Jera, guys.
I'm not even kidding.
Oh, that's cheap!
Takes just two out of three on the mother thing.
Let's do it.
Wow!
I want to keep this though.
Especially because our move speed is kind of bad without it.
Okay, move on.
I mean, this run is just easy.
I honestly don't see how we can lose.
And I'm not jinxing it, like this is a fact.
What's that?
Ants?
Oh my god, really?
Every map has been revealed for me so far, I think.
Almost every map.
What are these?
I've never seen these enemies.
Cursed?
Oh wait, but here's the thing, there's no charging, right?
Ah, but no, no, no, no, that's gonna fuck up my stuff probably.
I don't want to, yeah, it's gonna turn my stuff into a charge.
I don't want that.
I kind of want to go back and grab this room that I forgot.
We almost picked it up.
Wow, this is actually better than whatever it's called.
Brimstone.
It's more powerful, more versatile.
Brimstone does go through obstacles, it's spectral, right?
That's the big advantage.
That one tooth appears.
What is it with these teeth?
How many teeth?
Look at the way it's spreading to everyone.
Damn.
Thanks buddy.
I really should have Jared in here, shouldn't I?
Fuck.
I will never learn.
Trust there's gonna be a better time to use it, okay?
Okay, this will have been worth it.
Mom is here, have no fear.
Oh, treasure.
Oh my god.
Infested, infested.
Shot speed up, tears down.
That's bad for me.
And then we have a creep puddle and we can spawn.
No, I'll keep this.
Why is my stuff like...
Oh.
Weird, it doesn't lock on.
Okay, it does lock onto him.
Interesting interaction.
Carmones.
This one was infested.
Sure.
I'm being showered in blue hearts here, like...
Whoa.
Nothing can hurt me.
I will say, maybe I need a bit more damage.
Damage is a little bit low.
Did I get to the secret room here?
Wait a minute.
Oh no, I didn't.
Kill these guys.
Gives me more chance, for some reason.
Like, that's a weird interaction right there.
Why would that even give me more chance of an angel or a devil?
Makes no sense.
Okay, Geesh.
No, he dodged the laser attack.
Yeah, kill him.
This is just brutal.
Take that.
I think I'm ready for the final boss.
Put me in, coach.
Dank deaths.
We have a pretty high angel chance.
I won two, the pierce.
Dude, every map is revealed.
What is this challenge?
I can see forever, forever.
Give me more angel chance.
Actually, wait, if I destroy these.
Does not give me more.
Oh, I have no more bombs.
Whoops.
Kind of want to go back, actually.
I'll get in here.
Ooh, pills.
Damn it.
Abundance.
Kind of crazy that I can always go in the curse room with no repercussions.
Oh, shit.
Look at the wage spreads.
It's a little scary still.
Oh,
no more bombs.
Let's go.
I feel it.
Dude, was that flawless or what?
I mean, this run was just a smack down.
Uh, give me that one as well.
Boom.
Give me the trophy.
Easiest challenge of all time.
Robo baby has appeared.
Okay, so we're still like unlocking stuff with this.
That's awesome.
Let's do one more.
That was way too easy, man.
Waka, waka.
Am I battery, man?
Strange attractor.
Enemies and pickups are attracted to Isaac's tears.
Effect increases with shot distance and anti-gravity.
Tears will hover in place while pressing attack button.
Releasing it will shoot it.
Oh, interesting.
I mean, if they're gonna run into my shots, then... Hey, great start.
I
got...
Jesus.
How did that hit me, man?
Thank you.
Oh, we got here.
Look,
I have 3.7 damage.
That's kind of a lot.
Straight into it.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, they're gonna run into my... I just leave a trail of breadcrumbs here, and they're gonna run into it.
They kind of owned me a little bit there.
Sure.
Wait, does that take me to... one out of three?
Okay.
So I don't know what the little mom symbol means on the left.
I think it means maybe the last boss is mom.
You know, like, there's no treasure rooms.
There's no, yeah, there's no treasure rooms, but there is a mom.
Or something.
Yeah, I don't want anything here yet.
Wait.
Oh, they're... the hell, yeah, right!
Ludus!
They're coming to me.
Bob's curse.
Come here, come here!
Oh, that's so weird.
Luck up.
Oh, wow, okay.
Very lucky now.
And that's it for this floor.
Eight bombs, though?
This is good, because we can bomb things now.
Duh.
But, like, check this out there.
Right?
Not bad.
Kill him, too.
Did not gain any, uh, angel chance, but I think it's only worth it from floor two and onwards.
Because you start with Sera, right?
And then on floor two, it starts to go all the way up.
Hundred percent.
Jesus.
This is actually such a weird interaction.
Pull it down.
Honestly, I think I'm gonna go for the boss.
Just because, uh, you know, no buffer and we, we gotta, uh, we gotta, we gotta go.
Oh my god, what the fuck was that?
Why is he moving like that?
Whoa!
How do you dodge that shit?
Jesus!
That's impossible to dodge.
All right, cool.
I mean, that's just straight up impossible to dodge.
You need a buffer for that one.
Fuck.
Rip my demon.
No keys?
This is looking like a step floor, doesn't it?
All these red hearts.
Oh my god.
What?
Blow this up.
Oh, no key.
No!
No, this is so weird, man, because they're being attracted to me as soon as they charge.
Oh my god, really?
Dude, I mean, we're gonna have a lot of HP.
That's cool.
Black heart.
That could have been my buffer.
Kind of sad though, but you know.
Uh, secret room.
Right here.
How good am I at finding it?
Like, I feel like I just, I just know it now.
Oh man, I was hoping for a key.
Too bad.
Oh god.
You can kind of use it to bait them in with the magnet when you're charging it up, and then when they get close, you blast them.
That was a bit risky what I did there, but the idea is there, you know?
Come on.
Yeah, key.
Sick.
What do I want to use it on?
I think the shop room.
For sure.
With 19 coins.
The jar.
I mean, honestly, for me, that is only rolling with red hearts.
And there's two red hearts on the map right now.
I don't mind it.
Potato peeler consumes one red heart, contains a grand permanent cube of...
Ooh, that could also be interesting, actually.
I didn't think about that.
That could have been interesting too.
But we don't have enough money for both.
We almost do.
If I can scrounge up a little bit more money...
Nah, let's collect this.
And this one.
Moving on!
Okay, 100% demon now and no buffer.
This is actually kind of rough.
Oh, rip.
He came at me fast.
I think I just had to keep moving here, you know?
Leave a breadcrumb and let them walk into it.
That would have been better.
I can't get that chest out, but yes, I can.
Bible tracks?
Sure.
Not worth it, honestly.
Leave a trail of breadcrumbs.
Let them get magnetized into it.
Or not.
The way they came towards me.
Actually, kind of scary.
Normally, immobile enemies suddenly charge you.
Oh, let's do this.
I need pills.
Okay.
Wow, again?
I don't mind.
Liberty Cab.
Yeah, why not?
I think I like it more.
Grab this one, too.
Wait, this room has no meaning.
No reason to do anything there.
Oh, okay.
Dude, I'm really lagging keys here.
I want bombs or keys.
No!
Oh, this guy's camouflaged.
Purity.
Wait, what was that one?
Removes curses and brands.
Hey, you know what?
Why not?
How come it didn't remove the curse?
We have XL curse.
Maybe it doesn't make sense to remove that.
Dude, please die.
Oh, my God.
At this point, I've lost my angel privileges anyway.
You know what?
There's actually a strategy you can utilize here.
I'll show you.
So what you do is this.
Hold on.
You make a little pool, and then you walk away from it.
Because then they charge it.
The bigger the pool, the more magnetism, right?
So, gonna do this, and then walk away from it.
This is the way to play this.
You see that?
You gotta be fast.
Oh, not this again.
Dude.
Painful.
Such tanky enemies.
Make a little pool, and then walk out of the way.
Oh, I'm too slow.
Yeah, just go.
Gordy.
Oh, my God.
Dude, I don't know how to dodge this guy's attacks.
He's too fucking fast.
Yeah, this guy's impossible.
Holy shit.
He's not even the right boss.
Okay, this challenge is kind of hard.
Oh, my God.
I may have to use my...
Wait, I thought I could only spawn one at a time.
Okay, well, I guess they're all spent.
This is so awkward.
I may die here.
Oh, nice.
Nice.
Really difficult.
Honestly, move on.
Just go.
I feel okay about it.
I'm confident we can beat mom.
As long as we get some more healing.
Oh, this room is gonna kill me.
Oh, this is actually bad.
My fucking buffer.
Oh, I'm never getting angels.
Never.
Oh, my God.
This guy almost came at me at Mach 10.
Shit.
I'm not even sure what items I would like to get here.
Look at the way I'm keeping them inside.
With the magnetism.
Pay to play.
Not really feeling that one.
I mean, I do have a lot of money, I guess.
And we are nearing the end.
Maybe it's worth it.
I may come back and buy another key.
And there's the boss.
Oh, I don't know if I can... Okay, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
I'm gonna save my strength for mom.
This boss gotta be hard, man.
I can tell you.
I'm gonna have to use some bombs here.
Fuck.
Get poisoned.
Okay, okay, that was very effective.
Okay, you know what?
Let's just make a breadcrumb trail.
Come on.
Yeah, that's it.
Good stuff.
More tears, less shot speed, hell.
Yeah, okay.
That's fine.
Last floor.
We gotta get our healing up, and then we kick mom's ass.
Two for you, bye.
Jesus Christ.
There goes my demon chance.
I think this challenge may have been designed in such a way where you cannot find blue hearts.
Like, you cannot get buffers.
Because I haven't seen one.
Actually, that's not true.
I think I had one.
Or maybe it was a black one.
Rotten penny.
Um, no.
I'm good.
Oh my god.
Man, this room is gonna be problematic.
Wait, he came across!
I thought they couldn't cross.
Come on.
Good.
Ooh, I think I go back.
I love my character design on this one.
Oh yeah, we can attract them.
Uh, strength.
Thank you.
Right here.
Okay, I'll actually save the bombs for mom.
Jesus.
Whoa.
Oh my god, did you see that?
The gravity pulled the laser into me.
I gotta see what this is.
Oh, I don't know if I want to do that.
We don't need to... I could do it, actually.
Three and a half hearts.
Maybe a bit too risky.
I'm losing too much HP.
Oh no.
Okay.
Uh, hold on.
I gotta find a shop, actually.
Save my money for that.
I've gotta die in here.
This room is fucking insane.
I think it's over, guys.
That room was a fucking killer.
We need some... That's it.
Healing is what we need.
And a lot of it.
I hate these flying bitches!
Give me that.
Uh, Spider-Mod.
I would love to take you, Spider-Mod, but yeah.
There's no reason.
Fuck.
Just take it.
I, uh, yeah, this is not great, man.
We gotta find HP.
I can't... I can't do mom with this HP.
I just can't.
Oh no.
Oof.
Arcade!
Oh, I got no money.
But I do have bombs.
Uh, here's the plan.
Two gambles.
Come on, please.
Pardon me.
Dammit.
Okay, we're gonna blow you up, then.
Good.
Uh, maybe?
All right, fine.
Uh, this one also heals me.
Let's not forget, strength heals me.
Damn.
Okay, well, that's not too shabby.
We got a little bit of healing.
There's one more room we didn't explore.
Could get lucky.
One key.
Oh god.
Okay.
Show me the secret rooms.
Aha!
Well, I almost stepped on a spike.
I got two bombs left.
One for the secret, one for mom.
Uh, come on, please be full health.
Blow them up.
We have one more healing from the card.
Wait, another secret room.
I didn't even see that.
What?
The fool.
Okay, that's kind of huge.
Okay, here we go.
Wish me luck.
I need it.
Dude, having these extra sizes on tears actually helps.
Yo, get out of the way.
Gravity.
Magnetism.
It's a strong force.
Look at the speed at which I dodged these attacks.
Dude, this is easy.
I got it.
Oh, shit.
Okay, okay.
Calm down.
Dodge that.
Good.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Give me that.
See you later, nerds.
Death's touch has appeared.
Dude, we're unlocking stuff with these challenges.
I love it.
Keep going.
I'm on a streak.
I'm gonna do challenges until I lose.
The host.
Let's see what this is about.
The mulligan.
Can't just spawn a blue fly each time a shot damages an enemy.
Spawns blue spiders when taking damage.
Okay, and we have tick.
Got it.
So, I'm a host to all manner of organisms.
I like it.
Three health, standard setup for ice seeking.
Maybe there's a cheese configuration here, but he's too fast, I think.
The virus.
Poison touch and speed up.
Sure.
You don't want to get close to me.
I've got the virus.
Come to me.
Oh, bastard.
Okay, we got to prepare for the next floor in terms of buffers.
Yeah, no money.
One key.
One bomb, one key.
I'll save it.
I'm gonna wait until both of these minions spawn, I'm gonna death them.
I will death them until they die from it.
Bomb.
Yeah.
Actually, Insta kills them.
I'm scared.
I think staying at large range is actually better.
Which you can dodge that.
That was extremely nice.
Screw you.
Kind of want to go back and enter a curse.
We got the hearts for it.
Still no money.
I'm not even sure what the challenge is here.
B-rolls.
Oh,
interesting.
We're going to save that for an angel room.
I'm not going to open a chest.
I'm saving it.
Going, going, going, going.
We're going to one shot this challenge as well.
I mean, it's all about beating mom.
It's not really that hard, right?
Now, we don't have any buffers, so this is a little questionable.
One hit and we're going to lose it all.
Okay.
Yes, we'll do it, right?
Come on, spiders, kill him.
I have pretty good range.
Camouflaged?
I see you.
Please be AWAS.
Damn.
But I guess we can do that.
Curse is gone now.
We had the curse of whatever the fuck is going on.
Don't step on a spike now.
That would be catastrophic.
Nice.
Got no money, so why would I go in there?
Feels nice to have proper attacks now again.
All my spiders are gone though.
Would have been nice to have had that for the boss.
We got one buffer?
Let's do this!
Solid.
Oh yeah, no problem.
Clean.
Okay, I think I'm actually going to go in here.
Ooh, I hate it.
I don't like it.
What's that one?
Blackheart deals room-wide damage when taking hit.
That may be okay.
Maybe.
What was that one?
Chance to be... Okay, it's actually not...
This is probably one of the better ones in the Guppy universe.
But this one is arguably better.
Especially because it gives us one more buffer.
I'm taking that.
Oh, I forgot about my... Oh!
Why
did I realize after I took it?
Ah well, it's okay.
Pain.
I could have had Brimstone.
Shit.
I need a checklist every time I pick up a fucking pedestal item, man, that says, do you have something that you need to look at before you pick this up?
You know?
That's what I need.
Oh my god.
I'm being cornered!
Come here, you silly goober.
Okay.
This thing again.
I don't have money anyway.
Window shopping ain't fun.
What the...
That is actually not a bad idea.
I'm taking it.
I have tick!
Each habit I didn't tick off mine and crap off!
Why am I making all these weird mistakes right now?
It's only gonna make the victory sweeter.
I'm kind of stuck.
Boss has been acquired.
33% chance of demon.
Not too shabby, actually.
I think we go for it.
The fallen.
Why is he fallen?
Did he used to be a good guy and now he's not or something?
Oh my... Dude, I'm a god!
Oh, never mind, I'm not.
That's a good item.
Love that item.
Good item.
Why did I go in here, actually?
I don't have any HP.
Spirit of the night.
Everything's all right.
Uh, I mean... Flight?
Ooh, we can't do it, man.
I can't give up two of my hearts.
It's just... It's too much.
Generated... Okay, we could maybe go for that one.
Um... Fuck, I don't know, man.
I kind of want to do it.
Because it's gonna put us 2 out of 3 on Leviathan 2.
And having flight?
Nah, no, no, no.
We gotta play this safe.
Gotta play it safe.
We gotta make adult decisions here.
Uh, let's go.
Now I need to find a bit more damage and then I think I'm set.
Look at this fatty.
Like, what are these things even supposed to be if not tomatoes?
Like, look at them!
What are they?
They're tomatoes.
Disgusting tomatoes.
You know what's weird?
I only have 3.2 damage, but it feels like I have 6 damage.
I don't know why it feels like that.
Like, I'm doing good damage, but I don't have a lot of damage.
So, uh, what?
How?
I knew that was gonna happen.
I knew it.
I thought...
Dude, I could have had flight.
In hindsight, now, I mean obviously hindsight 2020, but I could have gotten that one, you know?
And that... that... man!
That's okay.
No, no reason to cry over things.
Shoulda, coulda, woulda, right?
Or something.
We gotta be thankful for what we have.
I'm thankful for the growth on my right eye.
I'm thankful for the HP I still have.
And the damage that I somehow have, even though it doesn't look like I have a lot of damage, but I somehow do, I'm thankful for that.
Lazy worm!
Um...
Right, never mind.
I have tick.
Haha!
Don't matter.
Oh yeah.
Soundtrack.
It's going hard.
Really want to step through those spikes just to see what that pill is.
Is that crazy?
Is that just me?
A buffer would be sick here.
So would mom's box.
Double... dude, double the effect of tick could actually be nuts.
Imagine.
Removes 30% health from the boss?
Ooh!
Not... you know what?
I'm gonna save.
Let's save a bit.
Oh no.
Just stay at range, stay at range.
Good.
Stay mobile.
T-Mobile.
Dropbones are not real.
They're never coming.
Real fortune.
Let's do it.
I don't know why I did that.
Thank you.
Mega fatty!
I'm gonna blow him up.
Actually, I'm pushing him into the TNT.
No!
He jumped right at the wrong time.
That's crazy.
Lucky you.
Nerd!
Bell for my... uh... bomb trick.
Okay.
Easy.
Okay, now we go in.
Because now I have an extra HP.
Poor Fabulon!
Dude, I hate these.
I hate both of these.
I hate them!
No!
I reject the demon again.
That's two demon rejections in one run.
Should have gone for the angels.
The black powder is maybe the worst item in the game.
Okay, maybe not.
The sprinkler probably takes the cake on that one, but it's bad, okay?
Shit!
I got hit twice there.
This room is gonna go hard.
Maybe.
Yeah, I don't know where all this damage is coming from.
I have no damage, but somehow I do.
How is it real?
Okay, we got flight.
If I need it.
Man, this is gonna be tough.
Good damage.
There must be some technique to kill these guys in an easier way.
Uh, I don't like this at all.
Ah, fuck you!
Fuck you!
Stupid inanimate objects!
Dammit!
Okay.
I can't be the only one who thinks those inanimate object enemies are incredibly difficult.
Jesus!
Like... oh my god.
Imagine if they had lasers.
What
the...
wow!
Yeah, just... what a room.
What a room.
Wait, they're somehow creating blood on the floor from a distance.
Maybe that's what they do.
That's their whole shtick.
Good.
It's not looking good, boys.
One and a half red hearts.
It's not good.
Okay, please.
Something good.
Uh, box of friends.
Creates a duplicate of each of Isaac's familiars for the current room.
Horrible.
I think I'm gonna buy that heart.
Compost duplicates each blue spider and fly... oh, I mean...
No, I only have one.
So I shall pick up some of the grand... nah, that's horrible.
I guess I'll take this.
I need everything I can get.
And at least we'll get a demon thingy.
Better than nothing.
I could get those bombs if I wanted, but I don't want to.
This one's gonna be tough.
I'm starting to feel the lack of damage.
The sun is massive.
We're saving that for mom.
Actually really good.
We may have to use it here.
I'm not sure how scary this guy is.
It's like the gray variety of this boss.
I don't know what he does.
Oh.
Oh my god, stop.
Oh my god.
Okay.
That's what we need to do.
No!
Why don't charge me?
Okay, good.
So hard!
More keys.
Uh, we're done on this floor.
We got the sun.
I'm ready.
The sun shall carry us to the end.
Arcade spotted.
Don't need that.
Oh no, please don't laser.
Okay, good.
Okay, we got a couple laser boys.
No,
I'm not happy about that.
I'm not happy.
Dude, I'm fucking finagling this.
Wow!
Nailed it!
This room again.
Here, this way you...
Gambling.
I'm okay.
Surprise.
If this guy charges me, I'm gonna be in trouble.
Okay!
We got a golden key.
Dude, things are kind of starting to look up here.
The challenge streak is alive, I think.
Uh,
oh, beautiful.
Something's wrong.
Oh well, too bad.
Oh my god.
Come on, mom, where are you?
Whoo!
That was close.
Oh, your mom is here, but that's not the mom I wanted.
Uh, wiggle, oh wait, I can't say it anyway.
Why am I even reading?
Oh my god.
Just move slowly, move slowly.
Okay.
Buffer, that's huge.
Not that we need a buffer, just more HP is good now.
I'll take this one too.
The moon!
The moon.
Okay.
Ew,
don't like that.
Ah, it took my last fucking inch.
Painful.
Give me that.
Come on, mom.
There you are, the last freaking door.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Not like this.
Please, please.
Mom, you gotta calm down.
I gotta be ready to use the sun.
We're gonna use it when we're at one HP.
Yeah, keep doing that, that's good.
I like that.
Oh my god, stop.
I mean, keep doing that, I like it.
Oh, that was a close one.
Oh wait, I have this?
Forgot I had that.
Well, okay, well, that's gonna make things a little easier.
And there it is, baby.
Three for three.
Who is the challenge master?
Tech five as a tech five?
What's that gonna be?
Dude, I can't wait to try tech five.
The family man.
Ew.
Oh, am I dead?
Wait.
Sister Maggie.
Brother Bobby?
Rotten baby.
What's the catch here?
Ah, we're Yulething.
I see how it is.
It's a Yuleth.
We're Yulething.
All right, that's the catch.
I'm like, this seems too good to be true.
It still kind of is, honestly.
This is very good.
Oh wait, we got a dad's key here.
We can totally...
Ah-ha!
Monster manual or...
What about the key, then?
Man, I would love to keep the key.
But now that you give me this, I mean, can I resist?
I can't fucking resist that.
Also, the monster manual is gonna be amplified because of my...
What's it called?
BFF.
Hmm.
Two out of three on that.
My pass is locked in most doors with special requirements.
I think I'll keep...
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna get another charge on my blue heart here.
Just so I have a buffer for the next floor.
Then we're gonna go into monster manual.
Just because we have BFF.
And we're going for army, right?
Full army mode.
We're not going that far anyway.
We're just going to mom, right?
So...
Actually, wait a minute.
There's no mom symbol on the left.
There's a little crying Isaac symbol.
This may not be mom.
This may actually be Isaac.
That is the end.
I like how I look there right after I say it.
In that case, maybe I'll keep the Bible then.
We'll see.
Yeah, this is gonna be interesting.
I'm not gonna gamble on that.
Oh god!
I didn't even see you!
I didn't see you!
Nice.
We got pills.
Obviously, I eat those.
Hey, nice!
I did feel a little slow, so this is gonna help.
Looks like I have giant ears, doesn't it?
But it's actually little guys.
For a second, I thought maybe my sister was called Maggie.
Okay, we got the buffer back.
You know what?
I'm gonna keep this Bible.
It's too good.
It's just too fucking good.
I can't let go of it.
Especially now that we're not going for Mom.
We're going for Isaac.
Still, though, it does say no treasure room.
Hey, cube of meat!
It's gonna be bigger.
Nice.
See, that's actually not bad with this character.
I like that.
100% demon, we got one buffer.
Life is good.
We're not done here.
Oh, I see.
And, dude, my familiars are doing a lot of damage, too.
Another buffer for me.
Could go in there, but I'm not going to.
I think this is gonna be a solid challenge.
Like, a solid as in, it's gonna be not too hard.
I think we're doing great.
Piercing and spectral, sure.
It's just a small percent chance.
I think the cube of meat just protected me from that jumping spider.
Oh, god.
Wait a minute.
The pin may be useless for me.
I don't know if that works with my familiars.
It's probably not, right?
I mean, it doesn't really matter.
Six coins.
Okay.
Blighted oval.
It's going to fall.
Wow, the damage is crazy.
What's with the damage?
Speed is good.
We can take a demon deal.
Contract from below?
Uh, no.
Okay, we don't know what this is.
False PhD is really good.
I need to try this.
Maw of the Void.
Consume thy enemy.
Grants an additional charged attack that creates a black ring around Isaac when released.
The ring deals rapid damage to enemies and cons.
I feel like I've had this before, though.
Dude, that's really good for me because I can't shoot anyway, so this is yet another way for me to do some damage, right?
Not bad.
Uh, I could also...
No, stop.
No more.
This is it.
We got 13 coins, though.
Time to spend it.
Oh, thank you.
14.
I'll take this.
And...
Ooh, that one.
Boom.
They call me the buffer man.
Buffer baby.
I can't...
Dude, watch.
That could have had 10 coins in there.
Don't judge.
Yeah, you see how there's more rooms up there now?
Means we're going for Isaac.
My ring is not strong enough for you.
Really should charge that up before I go into a room.
Yo, three out of three time!
But that's not gonna work on me, is it?
Satanic Viper!
I want that even more!
Wait, are they shooting two shots?
No, it's...
No.
Yeah, so it's kind of wasted on me, I guess.
This one's also wasted on me, I think.
Oh yeah, Satanic Bible.
Even better.
Getting all the Bibles.
Wiggle worm.
That's not gonna affect me.
It doesn't matter.
Fight room!
Wow, how lucky is that?
Solid.
I'm gonna blow this guy up.
Gives me more demon chance.
For reasons nobody knows.
Oh, I saw a tinted rock, but I can't get in there!
Maybe if I'm sneaky and I somehow destroy the rock from the other side?
No, I need flying or something.
Oh, can't access that anyway.
Ooh, battery pack!
It's kind of big.
It's not that big.
I'll come back.
So far, I think this challenge is a W.
We're gonna win it.
With the red fire out of here.
Especially with the buffers we have going on, right?
The Fallen again?
What's up with that?
Oi!
Shovel!
I don't need that.
No, that's not, that's not, no.
Nope, I'm good.
It's also costing a red heart to take.
I don't think I want that at all.
Flooded caves.
Oh, I stepped on the crab.
Ooh, what is that?
Maggie's faith!
Sister Maggie?
Grants an eternal heart at the start of each new floor.
Whoa!
I would love that.
I need flying.
Oh no.
I destroyed the black poop.
It's gonna be awkward to play against Isaac, though, with this build, I think.
But it's just about patience.
This Bible is gonna carry me.
Fragmented card!
Yes!
I like that.
Okay, my damage from the familiars is way more than my ring.
That is a solid amount of damage.
I'm gonna, I think I'm just gonna move on.
Uh, wait, wait, 26 bucks, though?
All right, it's an empty shop.
Too bad.
Vistula!
Ouija board!
This is useless for me.
Because I don't, it's gonna affect my tears and not my familiars.
Headless baby!
Now that sounds good.
Another familia to join the, join the club.
I like that.
Thank you, Sharon.
We're moving on.
Getting a little low on HP, though, but that's okay.
We have the satanic bibble.
Just gotta keep using it and not take damage.
We gotta save up some hearts for the final boss.
Precharge.
I gotta stop there a little bit.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Wow, boss discovered already.
Uh, I kind of want to do it.
This is gonna be mom, right?
Oh no, that's the next one, I guess.
Wow.
I gotta scratch my head.
There we go.
No!
Okay, not bad.
That'll do it.
Now, do I take the gamble here?
Dude, when there's a gamble, though, I'm kind of in.
You know, like, this could be really good.
Necromonicon.
No, thanks.
I'll keep my satanic bible, please.
Thank you.
Move on.
I feel good.
I feel good, man.
Now it's mom time.
Mommy.
I do wish my familius had a bit more attack speed.
He wants bombs, eh?
I can give him that.
Oh, no.
Drop some HP.
Okay.
Thanks.
Oh, dude.
Arcade?
Yeah, I got money.
Uh, yeah.
Just gamble the shit out of this.
This place now.
Oh!
Actually, I like that.
I'm gonna blow you up.
Tears up, range down.
Doesn't matter for me.
Oi!
Wow!
Damn nothing in the last, like, six?
That's crazy.
Lucky penny!
Man, if only I had a lot of red hearts, you know.
I could have done some fun stuff with stepping, maybe.
That was just itchy.
Nice.
Another stack.
Yeah, the circle of death thing I have is not that great.
Fuck!
Why did I spend all that money?!
Man!
Oh, it's not that good, actually.
Ah, never mind.
It's not that great.
I thought it was another Familia that would be, like, insane with my BFF.
Ooh, ooh!
Sick, sick?
That's a good one?
Meow.
Oh!
Okay.
I'm good, I'm good.
Take me back.
You know what I could do?
Here's what we can do.
No, I blew it up!
I was gonna go back and take all the hearts and get money.
It's fine.
Hey, Mom.
How's it going?
Honestly,
I think not making the circle is more DPS for me.
Because whenever I release it, they stop shooting.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on.
Yeah, I like that, I think.
Lovers, useless stuff.
I'll take that.
Let's get in here!
Let's do it!
Experimental treatment.
Stitches.
While held, it grants a Familia that can be controlled with the attack buttons and deals minor contact damage to enemies.
Activation swaps places with the Familia.
That sounds way too fucking complicated for me right now.
I need something simple.
Like a bozo.
A soul heart and a random chance to briefly apply fear or charm.
A chance to spawn a rainbow poop?
No.
A chance to spawn a blue fly each time a shot?
That is actually good for me.
Assuming that my BFF works with that.
And then we have large sit.
Here's the fire sit shot.
That deals 2x, Isaac's damage.
No, that's useless for me.
Lost fly.
Traces along the edges of walls and obstacles and deals contact damage.
I think that's good for me.
And monstrous tooth.
I think this is the one.
Wish me luck.
Wait, my damage is not great.
I'm gonna try and make it work though.
Oh god.
That was close.
Kill the little guy here.
Oh shit.
Where's this shield coming from?
Is that the multidimensional?
Whatever.
You gotta kill these little dudes.
This guy that's tracing the edge of the room, maybe it's not the best.
He's too far away from everything.
What's happening?
Oh, he's bombing.
Multidimensional, baby!
It's actually working!
It's working okay with my familiars.
Keep healing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, hey!
Walk backwards.
Man, my multidimensional is too far backwards.
Okay, okay.
These guys are gonna be tough.
Shit.
Why am I getting this shield?
I don't understand that.
Man, this shield just protected me.
Oh shit.
This guy's gonna do lasers, right?
We gotta kill him.
Nice.
He's down.
We have this guy up here now.
Whoopsie daisy.
Careful.
What the hell is that?
Oh, he's attacking the little fly!
That's what's happening.
Okay, we're losing a lot of HP here.
We gotta focus.
That fly's everywhere.
Oh, my god.
Big guy.
We may not make it.
May have been a mistake to come in here.
Shoot him!
Okay, good, good.
No, I got hit again.
How am I getting hit by that?
That's so bad.
Three hearts, man.
Okay, you do laser.
That means you die immediately.
Oh, my god.
No!
Kill him.
Oh, I almost walked into that.
Focus.
No!
Dry baby?
Sure.
Give me that.
That's gonna give me extra DPS, but I'm only at one heart, and I can't see nothing.
Fuck!
Oh, god.
This may be the end of the streak.
Focus.
Oh, god.
Yeah!
A heart, but I don't need that.
Oh, no, this guy's gonna kill me, man.
There is no way in hell.
I survived this one.
Wow.
Okay, we killed the worm.
There's another worm.
Give me some actual hearts, not the red hearts.
Come on.
Ah, man, fuck!
Good run.
It was a good streak.
I shouldn't have gone in there.
I was too sure of myself, you know?
It was a bad idea.
Okay, let's do normal runs, but first, I'm gonna take a break.
I'll see you in, like, five minutes.
I'm going to pick a random character, and we're going to win.
The streak is ready for me.
I could also... I wonder... It's kind of sad, because if I click random here, it's not really gonna include this guy in the pool, right?
That's kind of sad.
At least, I assume so.
We'll find out.
Random!
It's Cain.
He's here to inflict pain.
I like it.
I like Cain.
He's just, like, solid all around, you know?
Good chap.
Yeah, there's no batteries here to grab, guys.
I am empty.
The void of battery.
Charge.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wow, how did that... Oh, okay.
Wait, this guy's fart is not dangerous.
Neither is this guy's, okay.
That buffer is ready for the next floor.
You know what?
The only real challenge in these... I was about to say, wait, this isn't a challenge.
Never mind.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I'm in challenge mode right now.
Dude, how am I gonna kill these guys?
Slowly is the answer.
There we go.
One of them down.
Wow.
Oh my god.
This is Insano style.
Good.
That took a while.
Dude, I'm gonna go for perfection.
Imagine doing a run, not taking any damage all the way through.
I'm gonna try that today, guys.
I can't even say that with a straight face.
I can't even say that.
It doesn't count.
Okay, wait, it still doesn't count.
It's not red hearts, doesn't count.
Okay.
From the next room, we're gonna start counting.
It doesn't count yet.
More bombs, huh?
Okay.
Man, my buffer's gone.
Oh, that guy just killed his own friend with the spikes.
Didn't realize that could happen.
Pause is here.
Let's do it.
Oh, not... You know what this means?
It means we're gonna get the Steven item, and I hate that.
I don't like... I don't want this.
No way you hit me with that.
I may actually die here.
No!
Okay, I'm dead.
My fucking streak!
My streak of one!
Not like this!
Thank god he stopped.
Get away from me!
Okay, you got cheese configuration.
Wow!
I'm alive.
I don't know how I clutched that.
But I did.
Holy crap.
Alright, we gotta go heal.
The streak is alive.
It's okay.
Calm down, everybody.
No need to panic.
Stay calm.
And it's not too bad.
There's even a pill in there.
I want it.
It's also a key.
If I'm smart, I can get both.
Efficiency.
Hell yeah.
Whoa!
Ah, it doesn't reveal secret rooms, though.
I'm gonna get in here, too.
Wait, that's not gonna work, is it?
Maybe?
Nice!
I mean, not that I need the battery, but maybe I will need it.
Oh.
Huge.
That is huge.
I'm getting a little fatter, though.
That's okay.
We can walk that off.
I got six bombs.
I feel like I should be doing stuff like this.
Wow!
Buffers!
Okay, we're totally back.
We are so back.
Whoa!
Health up!
Ah, okay.
Still, though, not bad.
Great start.
Show me more secrets.
It's time for the fat kid to make his mark on the world.
So that pill should reveal, right?
Yeah, look here.
Another buffer!
Okay, guys, we're going for angels.
Then again, we do have a lot of red hearts.
Maybe we go for demons.
Demons is better.
Just to exchange some of that, right?
That makes sense.
I could also go in here.
Let's do it.
We're going in, baby.
I kind of want to see these areas in more detail, anyway.
Always the sewer place.
100% demon, but we have a big buffer.
So it should be okay.
I really need to fuck this up to lose that buffer.
Sometimes I do be throwing things, but I can't throw it that bad, right?
Actually, little Steven's stuff is homing.
Actually, not bad.
I kind of like you, little Steven.
Come on.
This is a weird room.
Look at the tiles on the floor.
Isn't that weird?
Dude, I love the look of our character.
Look, it's just a fat pirate.
That's what that is.
A fat and bald pirate.
This one may be worth.
Count boss already.
I think that's good.
We have a big buffer.
It's clog.
At least we're going to clear up the sewers here.
My nose is so itchy for some reason today.
Whoa!
That's a cool effect.
Okay.
I betcha I can probably use the active where you can, you know, you know the one.
Fucking toilet active.
Flush.
I can probably flush this guy.
I mean, he's a turd, right?
And that's what you do with turds.
Flush him.
Hey, speaking of flushing.
Yeah, he got flushed.
Definitely doing demons.
Trade my soul for money.
I don't think so.
Dude, I hate these.
I hate both of these, man.
What is it with these freaking deals today?
I'll take this.
Whatever.
Where's my brimstone at?
Ah, that's right.
I need to play a sasle to get that.
That's the only time I get lucky.
When I play normal mode.
Get a sasle and then you win.
These guys are not too scary.
Oh, that's mine.
But it was an enemy.
Kinda want to blow up all this poop.
Mystery egg.
I don't like that.
All gamble.
Mini mush.
Speed and range up.
Oh, mushroom.
I see.
Size down.
Okay.
I mean, not that fast.
Bit of speed.
Ever heard anybody?
Man, I don't feel like anything in here.
Yeah.
Horrible.
We're not that fat anymore.
We're like small and fat, I guess.
I'm tempted to do this.
But, nah.
I'm going to look for a secret room.
It's always in the center.
Ooh, we got money for the shop.
Why didn't that give me a chance for demons?
I shouldn't waste my bombs too much.
Oh, it's because I already did the demon, right?
Using an uncharged item will exchange half a red heart for each missing charge.
I don't want that.
I'll save my money.
Imagine I get converter though.
Okay, moving on.
I could also still... nah, that's not worth it.
I'm rich already.
I know if I picked it up, I'm only going to find bad items in the shops anyway.
Oh,
right!
Dude, we should do this, but not yet.
Not yet.
First, we clear everything.
I kind of want to look for tinted rocks.
I haven't seen any of those in a while.
Where are thou hiding?
Okay, good.
Here we go, please.
Okay, compass?
That's fine.
Don't mind that.
Better than not using my money.
Blue flames?
That's totally worth to try and destroy.
Ah, I only hit one of them.
I kind of knew it was badly placed when I placed it.
What's with this green fly?
Okay, I guess we're going for it.
33% angel chance or demon, I mean.
I
have okay damage here.
Feels good.
Nice.
More speed.
Come on.
Oh, I thought it was the satanic.
Two spooky is actually okay.
I like that one.
Here's the thing though, if I take this, then if we find a library, it's a guaranteed bookworm, right?
So that could be worth it just for that.
And we get to use it.
Because we don't have an active anyway.
Dude, I'm doing it.
We're doing it.
I'm not done on this floor.
And how much damage does it give me?
It doesn't say.
Oh, Ludovico!
What the fuck?
No, no, how did I?
Okay, uh, wait, wait, is this actually, is this what I want?
Yeah, I want it.
Oh, yeah.
It's going to be a little weird.
But it's okay.
Balls of steel.
Nice.
Huge.
There's a treasure room we haven't seen yet.
There's a flame.
What's that room?
Nice.
Blood donation.
Battery.
This is, this is weird.
I guess I could do it.
I have a couple hearts back there.
Why not?
Yeah, good stuff.
Dude, I'm so fast.
One.
Another one down here.
We actually have a third one ready as well.
Uh, yeah, do one more.
Oh, there's also one in here.
Totally missed that one.
Grab this one.
And that one.
And that's not it yet.
There's more.
Just hide in the corner.
Don't be a hero.
Maybe I should actually be using my mouse for this.
Wait, let me actually, okay, I'm going to give this another shot with the mouse.
This may be the time.
You know, I wonder if I get more shot speed, if it's going to run towards my cursor faster.
Right?
Because right now you see how there's a delay when I move it.
It's kind of fucked up, right?
Maybe with more shot speed that will do it.
Lower you up.
Was there anything else in the shop?
Kinda.
No, you know what?
I'm going to regret it.
I'm going back to keyboard.
I'm going to regret this.
I just know it.
Where's my... Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Yeah, let's... Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Oh, shit.
I'm so okay.
I need to be hiding in corners.
Oh, I almost ran into him.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
That's scary.
This is risky.
Nice.
I guess range doesn't matter.
Hold on, I got a sneeze.
Man, I swear to God, they're killing me.
I'm scared.
Whoa.
Oh, knife piece.
Right.
I'm going to die.
I don't know where my projectile is.
Fuck these rooms, man.
Shit.
I couldn't see my fucking projectile.
There was too much crap in that room.
Kane again?
Sure.
There's not much RNG in the RNG generator.
I'm trying to think, why am I even doing that?
Why am I going into that dimension?
What's the point?
What am I going to get out of it?
Maybe nothing.
Whoa, shit.
La, la, la, la.
I mean, I ain't got any money.
It doesn't really matter, does it?
Go.
I was trying to get into the door, but it's closed.
Because we weren't done.
Bummer boy.
Oh, I hate that one.
Horrible.
Why are you coming all the way over here?
I don't understand the movement of these things.
I thought you were going in a predetermined pattern.
Fuck.
Uh-oh.
What are these guys doing?
All right, look at all this here.
Yeah.
Satisfying.
Definitely getting in there.
I kind of like these bombs.
It's going to make it much easier to hit bosses with it.
Are they going to spawn a little bastards when they die?
Skeletons?
Sometimes they do.
That's the boss.
We got one buffer.
This is good for next floor.
As long as we don't take damage here.
Oh, wait.
It's a weird version of the Duke.
I don't know what he's going to do.
Because he spawns those guys.
I'm going to bomb him.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Feels every floor tile with poop.
Hold on a minute.
Justice.
Maybe I'll take that.
That was Isaac's coins.
Yo, actually, I have 10 already.
Teleport to the devil or angel room.
Oh, my God.
Okay, hold on a minute.
This one first.
Nice.
That's so huge.
That's a good first floor so far.
So here's the thing.
I wonder if I if I do Joker now, right?
It's going to take me to the demon room on this floor, which is actually insane because normally you don't have access to one on this floor.
Thirty four coins.
I should have done the poop first and then because I'm probably going to get coins here against this play.
I messed it up.
Yeah.
See, there's.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bad decision.
I wasn't thinking.
It's going to take forever to clear.
You hit two at the same time.
It's not that much coin we're getting in before I get like two 10 coins.
Yeah, this is the I regret.
Now I need some insane shops later on and this one will be amazing.
Shit.
Okay, 44 coins.
That's nice.
No, they're question marks.
Okay.
Damage up.
We're taking the other one.
We're not a pussy.
We're going to do it.
We're doing it.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
We're going for it.
Okay, well, not the greatest stuff we got here, but you know,
pentagram.
It's decent.
We're going.
I think we may be in trouble here.
This was not a good idea, was it?
Oh, no.
What have I done?
The good news is we don't have any red hearts.
So we're going to have good angel chances.
Speak enough.
We need to get angels now.
No more demons.
We don't have anything to trade.
Unless we get more blue hearts.
Why won't you die?
Okay, there we go.
Whoa.
Good enough.
Shop, huge.
PhD.
Better pills.
Lock.
Create a duplicate of each I6 familiar.
Maybe could be good.
I have one familiar.
What do you even do again?
Fire spectral tears.
I mean, I don't have anything else.
May as well do it, right?
May not have been worth it there, but whatever.
Oh, that is a rock.
That is so big getting that.
No, there was an enemy in there.
What?
Come on.
That's unfair.
I need more ways to spend my money.
Oh, my God.
His head disappeared and reappeared.
I'm in trouble here.
Colostomia?
That's a bag with poop in it.
Oh, my God.
I bet I can't stand in that poop mist.
Oh, no.
I'm in trouble here.
Wow.
I think it's over.
The game is too fucking hard for me, man.
I feel like normal mode.
I can't win anymore.
It's just...
It's too hard.
Just can't win.
Can't even get past four floors.
Magdalene.
Let's try and do some stepping.
This is a good character for that.
Yeah, okay.
Bob's curse.
And the worst part is I feel like I'm getting pretty good starts, you know, but I just can't win.
I'm too shit at the game.
Like, what's this?
Tech five!
It's still being tested.
Fires random lasers in addition to Isaac's tears.
Huh.
Okay.
Let's see how that goes.
Seems okay.
It has a... not spectral.
What is it?
Piercing.
That's nice.
Monstro.
Yeah, it's definitely doing good damage.
What happened there?
I think it just had a random effect applied to him.
Key.
Latch key.
I mean, this is a good start.
This is a really good start.
Let's see how it goes with this one.
Feels like there's some kind of weird cooldown on my tech five.
Like it needs to... or maybe just completely random.
Could be.
Shop.
We got seven coins.
Eight.
Ooh, spider mod.
I want it.
This is also really good.
No, but I actually... I want to keep my active.
Yeah, it had to be one of those two.
Wheel of fortune.
I didn't mean to do that, actually.
Roll it up.
Appeal.
Verb.
I'll keep it.
Moving on.
Now I really wonder how my current tech five is going to sort of scale up with the items that I find.
Right?
Like if I get more tears or more damage, that's what that one's obvious.
But if I get more tears or shot speed, is that going to affect it in various ways, you know?
We'll find out.
Looks like some of my shots are spectral.
No, no, nevermind.
They're not.
Good try.
Blow it.
Ooh, nah.
Dude, what is it with all these rooms and things I can't get to?
What?
Oh, little bastard.
Okay, well, I'm getting a bunch of money.
Min Min.
Man, being able to destroy these with the tech helps a lot.
Little guys.
I think I just need to go around in a circle.
No, I lost all my demons.
Fuck you, man.
I feel like puking.
Burp?
That's the sound I make when I puke.
Dreamcatcher.
Man, fucking items in the shop suck ass.
Like, there's never any good items in the shop.
But I'll take it.
May as well do it.
Yeah, give me some bombs.
I do want to save two keys at least.
Oh.
Okay, what is it gonna be?
Bedazzle me.
Chocolate milk replaces tears with a charge shot that increases in size and damage the longer it is held.
Uh oh, I wonder if that's gonna replace my freaking tech 5.
I'm gonna do it.
Okay.
Alright, I like that.
Not too bad.
Eh, okay.
I was fearing the worst.
We could step.
But that would mean removing a buffer, which is not the greatest.
Right there.
No?
Okay, right here.
Yeah!
Oh, I should probably just release this.
Triggers the effect of the card held without consuming it.
Uh, man, that's a shitty item.
Unless, dude, imagine, we find the sun.
Huh?
If we find the sun, this could be insane.
Because that would be pretty much a yum heart, but times infinite.
Right?
This item could be crazy with a sun.
I'm gonna try it.
We're gonna try and see if we can get a sun.
We'll see how it works.
Uh, wait, huh?
No.
That'll be a waste of an active to use that.
Actually, put it now.
Imagine this.
I find a pill.
I find health up, right?
I eat the health up, I take verp, and then I get infinite health up.
Huh?
Think about that.
Ho, ho, ho!
Infinite health!
I cracked the game.
Okay, I like this.
I still feel like my damage is kinda... ew.
The flush, no thanks.
Jacob's... oh!
Now I wish I didn't take the one that makes it into one giant bowly.
Crap.
I mean, I can still do this, right?
So maybe not too bad?
Yeah, I like that.
Hey, look at this one!
Thanks.
It's gonna be the electricity run.
Oh no, am I really gonna try that again?
Fuck!
Wait, I forgot what the point is.
So you do that and you get a knife piece.
And the reason you want that is to go through the meaty door to go somewhere that I forgot what's gonna give you.
I don't even know if that's gonna be worth it.
Compass.
Again.
I don't have money anyway.
Let's do it.
Wormwood.
Oh, you bastard.
Where are you?
Okay.
I think it's better that I spam the button.
Ah, not sure.
Dude, I nailed that.
Heck yeah.
Demon?
Yes, sir.
The pact.
Tears, damage, too.
Yeah, I like.
Some good old damage up stats.
And I like it.
Let's go in here.
But not yet, not yet, not yet.
Before we leave, I want to do this part.
Where's the... there, okay.
This way.
Wait, don't know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I can fly.
Right.
Grab everything I can.
Double check there's nothing I missed in here.
Okay.
Verb, verb.
Oh, shit, I'm scared.
Good.
Knife piece one.
Wow.
Did you see that?
I could have died immediately there.
What is this room?
I'm scared.
Dude, if that was a spiky chest, I would have been dead.
I can't open chests.
It's too dangerous.
What's happening?
Where are they?
Okay.
They're dead, they're dead.
We got to go, we got to go.
Oh, I may die to this.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, my God.
We did it, nice.
Nice.
Verb.
Show me what's good in the shop.
Nothing.
Kind of creepy with the reflection on the hanging guy.
I will say that.
Okay, we're leaving.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Get me out of here.
Yes.
Oh, we're safe again.
Oh, that's scary.
Scary stuff.
You know what?
I'm going to start writing this down, actually.
Hold on.
I need to, because in the future, you know, I just got to write it down.
I'm going to copy this.
We're going to say hula.
Hula.
No.
What would the title be for this?
Let's say, if you go to downpour and then go inside mirror with flying, you can find knife piece one.
Boom.
Let's just note it down for the future so I don't forget that.
This is like the point.
This is why you want to do that.
You want to get the knife piece.
That's why you go in there, right?
We actually have some healing here, so let's just do this.
Unfortunately, I probably should have collected these hearts while I was flying.
Ah, but I can't.
Yeah, that wouldn't have mattered.
Give me some good coins.
I'll take this.
I do wonder what happens if I touch the fire again now.
Okay.
Now what?
I go back.
I'm still flying.
I don't like that.
I dislike it quite a bit, I got to say.
Maybe I can use the flying for something, such as...
no, no, no, that's not a secret room.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm too scared to touch the machine now.
Get the bombs?
Yeah?
Not bad.
What was in here?
Could get the compass, or this one?
I think I like this one more.
Buddy in a box.
Hopefully, I'm not gonna stay flying.
Hopefully, I turn into a normal boy when I go through here.
Be good to me.
Fuck, dude.
It's over.
I ruined the run.
We may need to kill another boss to get out of this.
Maybe that's the condition.
There's no way I killed the boss here
without...
yeah, without random.
Whoever coded the RNG with that randomizer doesn't know what he's doing.
It's not random.
It just ain't.
Wrong RNG function has been used.
BOGO bombs.
I mean, I like Cain.
It's just, he's kind of boring.
Like, he's just kind of, there's nothing going on with him, right?
Nothing special about him at all.
What I mean is there's no gimmick.
Nice!
Oh, what a useless crawl space.
There's also a tinted rock there.
So how much you want to bet I will not find a bomb now.
Just the law
of the
Finally.
Crazy room.
I go.
Maybe a speed run.
There you are.
The belts.
I mean, 1.6 speed.
I will never need more now.
I'm done with that.
Whoops.
Still no bomb.
Maybe here?
We're gonna find a plus five bombs in here.
I can't get to it.
I can.
It worth.
There's the bomb!
Luck smiles upon me.
Okay, we got a buffer.
Good.
Now I'm happy.
We leave.
Oof!
Ah, this way.
There was also a shop here, wasn't there?
I got 11 coins.
There wasn't anything in there I wanted, I think.
No.
Go.
Okay.
Let's focus.
Downpour one.
Dude, I hate these flies.
Oh, you guys are enemies.
I mean, please keep doing that.
I love when you do that.
Sponsored large bomb.
Okay.
Right there.
I don't like that item.
Hey, if I go here, they're gonna.
That's actually a cool strat.
Oh, what the.
Okay, we're not done.
Can I make them walk into this?
No.
Nice hair.
Boss.
I could reroll, but I would need a bit more money for that.
I got to go while I still have a buffer.
Is it always going to be wormwood and downpour?
Something's very wrong.
Oh, my God.
Are you gonna do the spiky thing?
Not yet.
There it comes.
Oh, my God.
I couldn't go north.
Holy shit.
Random pill.
Again?
Ew.
We're going to go angel because absolutely fuck these demon rooms.
They have given me nothing today.
What a waste.
All of them.
Also, I don't have any HP to give.
So there's that.
God,
please delete these enemies from the game, man.
And infuriating to play against.
Jesus.
What do we have here?
Oh, never mind.
We got a party.
A little Loki.
Man, I don't like that.
Whoa, that's a crazy pickup.
Nice.
I'll take this.
Split shot.
What?
Tears split in two on contact.
They do?
What does that mean?
Isn't it going to do the same amount of... Wait, I'm confused.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Aha.
Right.
Very tiny split.
They don't really split.
They sort of spawn tears on each side.
That's what it looks like to me.
I feel like I'm way too fast.
Nice damage.
We like damage.
Oh, no.
There goes my buffer.
There comes my buffer.
I'm leaving.
He almost ran into the fire because I'm too fast.
Down we go.
Okay, so here's the problem now.
We need to find HP.
Otherwise, none of this is going to matter.
Like, two hearts.
It's just not good enough for me.
I will end up dying.
Damage right now is good.
Survival is what we need.
We got this fire here.
Oh, wait.
We got some bullshit.
Oh, you bastard!
Throw in pots at me.
Oh, I can't get in there.
I think it's worth it to destroy this.
I need that buffer, man.
Chemical Peel.
That's pretty good.
I think I want that.
Yeah, that's straight up just like 50% damage sometimes.
Yeah, look how often that happens.
Damage is very good now.
Oh, shit.
God, do I hate these enemies?
Please.
There we go.
Blow that up.
Another buffer for me.
What the?
What is that?
Card reading a link to your future.
Spawns two portals at the beginning of each floor.
These portals may lead to the boss room, treasure room, shop, or secret room.
The portals disappear upon exiting the starting room.
Or spawns only one portal in chapter four and later.
Ha!
Okay.
That's cool.
If we happen to find a lot of money, we can come back and re-roll.
Oh,
my God.
Here we go.
We got buffer.
Yeah,
he spawns these little bastards.
Oh, God.
Come on.
Caleb.
Nice.
Huge.
Uh, tear shots.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's good.
The Chariot.
That's also good.
I think we move on.
I don't have enough bombs.
We got to find another bomb.
And also, I want to go into the mirror.
Yeah, so that would be there, but no mirror detected, so probably here.
Yep.
Honestly, let's just do it.
In we go.
Let's find the boss room.
I see where it is.
That's kind of scary.
Oh, there's more.
We go straight for the... Oh, no.
But not like this.
Oh, my God.
I am so focused.
Holy shit.
Tears up.
That's nice.
A knife piece.
Come on.
Oh, no.
No.
Oh, you're not going to spawn more of those.
Oh, my God.
Uh, this way.
Kyo!
Kyo-do!
We're fine.
Is it spiky?
It's not.
Uh, go!
We need to nail this now.
It's me and me and I'm going to die!
Okay.
Kill him.
Keep moving.
Min, min, min, min, min, min, min, min.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
Yeah.
Now we get out.
I don't want to spend another second in here.
And we will never touch the fire again.
Give me that key.
All right.
Let's move on.
Nice.
Um, I'm actually going to take this.
Just another buffer, you know?
Play it safe.
We're going in.
Let's do this.
Wish me luck.
Oh, here we go.
Uh, I need to read this real quick.
Cart reading.
Two portals.
Boss room, treasure room, shop or secret room.
Right.
Okay.
Nice.
Secret room.
I wouldn't have minded the boss actually there.
Because we have a buffer right now.
Oh, shit.
Um, paperclip is actually not too bad.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Like, I don't remember what these guys do.
I have to relearn all of this.
Go back here.
No, I hate that.
Take this.
Boxes.
Terrible.
What do we have here?
Potato Pila.
Hey.
Actually, what is it with these?
I've gotten such good pills, man.
Can't complain about luck about that for sure.
I've had my fair share of luck on that.
Careful.
What the fuck?
I thought he was friendly.
There goes... I think we're done, man.
How am I going to beat the last boss here?
The guy that runs on rails.
Without taking damage, it's not going to happen.
This guy is way too crazy.
But I have good damage, so maybe.
The damage is solid right now.
What the hell?
Yeah, there goes my angel chance.
Along with all of my HP.
I haven't even damaged it once!
Can't fucking hit this guy.
Come on, focus!
Fucking hell.
Yeah, okay, dude.
You just suddenly go to fucking Mach 9 out of nowhere.
Sure.
Game is too hard.
Why am I even picking random?
It doesn't make any sense.
The game is like, you need to play this guy right now.
Something amazing will happen, if you do.
Nothing amazing has happened yet.
God, I feel so weak now.
Uh... Oh, I have the lost!
I hate that so much.
At least it's the first floor, so it's not going to be big.
What makes you larger?
Shit.
Guess my luck ran out on the pills.
Distant admiration.
Why not?
That's actually decent damage.
Oh!
Not bad.
Good amount of money.
Wait,
how did I get hurt?
Dumped?
Oh, nice, nice.
Yeah, push that into you, dumbass.
Oh, come on.
So we've been here, we've done that.
Have we done that?
We have done that.
Just double-checking.
South, we go.
I'm gonna blow them up.
Okay, 12 coins.
Wow!
This is it!
We've done it!
No, wait, three more coins.
Okay, we can get it, right?
We should be able to get it.
Okay, focus now.
This is the run.
Maximum focus.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, no, no coins though.
Please.
I need it!
Ah, dude, come on.
Don't tell me we're not gonna get it.
Please.
Okay, we got four poops in here.
We could have a chance of getting two coins.
I'm gonna save it for the end.
Oh my goodness.
Wow.
And you're done.
Okay, wish me luck.
Okay, maybe we miss some rooms.
I could also- Yo.
Shit.
Uh, it's gonna be hard to find secret rooms when I can't see the map.
But I can sort of map it out in my brain, I guess.
Probably here.
Shit.
Uh, maybe to the left there?
I can also- Oh, actually here.
Yeah.
No.
Okay, come on.
Coin me.
Dude.
This is the run.
Okay, okay.
We even got our luck.
Sick shit.
Go back and grab it.
Yoink.
Now we just need some blue hearts.
And then we are rolling.
Maybe I'll even do some stepping or... The world is my oyster pretty much now.
Uh, go.
Oh, hello there.
Guarding the entrance area.
A plot donation.
I don't know why I did that.
I can't use it.
Oh well, that's fine.
Downpour.
Morten salts.
Uh oh, what is this?
This guy has something in his mouth.
Okay, what are we gonna get here?
Stick my top?
Or question mark?
I think we're gonna go for this one.
I like it.
I really- Oh, I don't have any bombs, man.
I don't have any keys.
We need money to make money here.
What the?
Weird room.
Did they stay down?
They stay down.
Lost demon.
Right before the boss as well.
That is just so unfortunate.
And where's my blue hearts at?
Oh, it's this guy again.
Don't even have bombs for him.
Dude, if I hadn't taken that damage out there.
Shit.
I fucking killed that.
So sad.
There's probably a blue heart in there.
Okay.
I can't even get that.
Man, don't do this to me.
We're not done on this floor though.
There's more.
There's not a lot more though.
One coin?
Yeah.
Mine's always gonna be like this.
That's a very tiny floor, by the way.
Okay, we're gonna go in here.
I didn't want to have to do this, but here we are.
Whoa, conversion therapy.
Pills.
Yeah.
No, I, there's a battery.
There's a battery.
I'm getting the battery.
Yes.
Yep, yep, yep.
Oh, but we're gonna have very little HP though.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's fine.
We just need to heal.
It's okay.
Calm down.
We got this.
Okay, just focus now.
Keep it up.
This is to run.
Drus, and we don't have a key.
I really want to get in there.
You gotta key me right now.
Okay, bomb is also decent.
This room again.
I, you know what?
We gotta do that.
See, calculate it.
Damn, no key.
We got these weird smiling poops.
But, but they were friends or something.
Yeah, it's, I don't understand this.
Did they follow me?
Oh yeah.
All right.
Wow.
Got a bomb there.
What about keys though?
Man, this is so evil.
Come on.
Oh, what is that?
A small rock.
Damage up, speed down.
Okay, I mean, that's actually pretty good, but I need healing.
That's what I need.
Oh God.
Full health.
Come on.
Not like this, man.
Finally have the converter.
Don't fucking kill me like this.
Give me healing.
You can see a million hearts.
Now I see none.
What is this?
Fuck, man.
The one run, I finally get an S tier item.
You know?
God damn it.
You're so unlucky.
At least we got a treasure room right here.
Oh, I haven't seen that in a while.
Okay, actually, I thought that was the bandages.
That's fine.
BFFs, mempico, I mean, all these are great, but I don't have money.
Yet.
That was a bit risky.
Oh, library.
No key.
I'm not gonna get in that library, am I?
The Isaac gods have deemed it so.
It's Larry.
I'm tempted to bomb them, but I want to conserve my bomb.
Good.
Yeah, nice.
Shitty item, though.
Maybe.
Retrovision.
Okay.
Maximum buffer has been achieved.
That's not bad.
It's solid.
And we got a key.
Okay, things are turning around.
Library, here I come.
I hate the way my character looks.
Oh, all the eyes.
Disgusting.
Book of shadows.
That one is terrible.
This one is, I mean, not too thrilled about these.
This one, maybe.
We can use it to go into curse rooms and stuff.
Not the worst.
Okay.
Maybe here.
That was my last bomb.
I took a chance.
Oh, wait, I can't go in here.
I honestly don't know what I'm gonna get out of that anyway.
Okay, I'm gonna get a knife piece.
I get to fight a different boss, but so what?
Like, I already beat the boss.
Probably not gonna change anything.
Oh!
Okay, that was mean.
See here.
Oh, it's... It disappears when you enter.
I was like, I'm gonna get in, grab whatever's in there, and get out real fast, you know?
Because it's 10 seconds.
Nope.
Not how that works.
Only one buffer.
Uh, this shield, I can't attack with it, right?
Maybe I can.
Let me try.
Hey, I can.
Okay.
Honestly, kind of worth it to destroy that one guy.
To the worst enemies in the game.
Oh, good riddance.
I got a bunch of horse lying around.
Could be some stepping action.
But then again, I mean, we have the blue heart and I want to keep it for the buffer, right?
So, in reality, unless I have a converter, I will pretty much never step.
That's like the rule I have put for myself.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Charge me?
Okay, okay.
Uh, that one... we're going for angels.
Just move.
Demons suck.
Like, lately, I feel like 80% of the demon items are kind of bad.
Never find good stuff.
I think that was all my buffer.
I only have red hearts now.
Ripped my chances.
Like, I swear to god, these rooms are harder than any bosses.
It's a really uneven difficulty situation here.
Like, some of these random-ass rooms are just impossible not to take damage in.
It's because some bosses are, like, very predictable, right?
I think I lost my eternal heart.
This is fun.
This boss is actually really cool.
Ah!
Ew!
Scared.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Ah, wait, I'm dead?
Oh, shit.
I'm still alive.
I can't win, dude.
It's too hard.
I think I'm just not good enough, guys.
The game has gotten too difficult for me.
I can't even get to mom.
I think it's over for me.
Yeah.
I told you from the beginning, I just can't do bullet hells, man.
It's too much for me.
I don't know why it's gotten so... or not expensive.
Difficult, all of a sudden.
Like, why the fuck is the game suddenly so difficult?
I don't understand.
You know hit bosses now?
Yeah, one boss.
But, like, 80% of all the rooms, I just can't do it, man.
I'm just not fast enough.
There's too much shit on my screen.
I can barely see where my character is.
Hard to see what's going on.
You know?
I wouldn't say it's a knowledge issue, blue baby.
Because most of the time I know what I'm supposed to do.
I just can't execute it, you know?
Maybe focus on the normal floors instead of going the alternate way?
I mean, I could.
But I feel like I... yeah, I don't know.
Here's the thing.
The fact that you just said that already kind of killed one of my theories that I had.
Like, the thing is, I don't know what I should be focusing on, pretty much.
You know?
Like, in my mind, I need to go to the new areas to unlock new things.
Yeah, the challenges are a lot easier, man.
Like, normal game is way harder than challenges.
The challenges should really not be called challenges.
They're a cakewalk compared to this.
It's crazy.
I guess I still have a lot of challenges.
Yeah, I guess I've been doing the first ones, right?
The hardest challenge was the solar system so far, for sure.
There
were a lot of doubters when you did the walk-a-walk-a challenge.
Well, which one was that?
What was that one?
I forgot.
I did three today and I did a fourth one and I failed that one.
I forget what the walk-a-walk-a was.
Is that the one with the Pac-Man challenge?
What?
Attraction?
Oh, that one!
Right, yeah.
That one was actually kind of difficult, but I clutched it in the end.
True, true.
I mean, if you guys are saying I should do whatever to get unlocked, if it doesn't matter what I do, then fine.
Then it's okay.
Then there's no reason to do the alternate path or whatever you said.
Right?
Perfect.
Because I just want to get more unlocks.
I want to get more items because I feel like every single run I do, I see the same items.
I feel like I've unlocked 100 items, but it feels like I only see 20.
You know?
I did unlock stuff today, mostly from challenges, Yumu.
I don't think I unlocked a single thing, maybe one thing from normal gameplay.
I did think about the tier list of items, but then I realized it's going to be a little challenging to do because one, I would have to go through all the items in the menu that I have unlocked and then import them into the tier list website.
It seemed like kind of a crazy thing to do.
You know what I mean?
Oh yeah, I need to play more greed.
That's right.
I want to do more greed.
I actually kind of forgot that existed today.
What is my next playthrough going to be?
You mean like a different game?
Well, I said in the beginning of this stream, I was thinking about either Sims 4 or Hitman World of Assassination.
Something along those lines, but I could change my mind to something completely else.
So I don't know, but whatever it is, I'm going to play it next to or alongside Isaac.
Because I just want to keep unlocking new items.
I want to get new cool builds going.
That's like the main fun factor for me.
You know, like when you get a super cool build going in the Binding of Isaac, it is like fun unlike any other fun.
I just love it when you get that going.
And then on the other side, when you get a string of shitty runs where you just don't get anything nice, or if you die at something stupid, it's just like, oh, you know.
MewGenix is also like that.
Well, I wouldn't be surprised.
It's the same developer, right?
And it's the same kind of fan base.
Love that game.
That loves this game.
Shitty runs make me appreciate some items I wouldn't have thought about.
That's how I feel about challenges.
Challenges make me realize that some items are actually really good.
Like if it wasn't for the solar system, I wouldn't have realized that those flies actually do a shit ton of damage.
And I never would have utilized it, you know?
I'm better than you and you have 200 hours in Isaac?
Well, I almost have 200 hours.
No, I don't.
I have 131.
But still, I wouldn't say I'm that good, man.
I have a win streak of minus five right now or so.
I've never had a win streak more than two, I think.
You know?
Recently had a run in Icyc with a combination of items I've never seen before.
And I have over 2,000 hours in that game.
I mean, if you just look at the numbers, chances are you're gonna get a unique run every time.
Right?
If there's like a thousand items or whatever, like, you're gonna get a unique run pretty much all the time.
It's like a deck of cards.
64 cards, right?
If you shuffle it, seven or eight times, it's gonna be in an order never before seen in the history of the universe.
It's gonna be the same with this game.
Then again, there are some limitations because some rooms can only have a subset of those items, so maybe not quite the same analogy, but you know what I mean, right?
Oh yeah, 52.
What's your favorite milk type item?
I don't know.
That was considered a type in itself, but I don't know.
Like, can you give me some examples of some items I've had?
Do you mean the one with... actually, I don't know.
So I... I have no idea what those mean.
I guess I've had them before, but I don't know what they do, so I couldn't tell you.
Oh, chocolate milk, almond milk, regular milk.
I mean, in real life, I would say chocolate milk.
In the game, I don't know.
In real life, it's chocolate milk, for sure.
I love that.
I don't really drink normal milk in real life.
I put it on my cornflakes, but other than that, not really.
Or I use it in cooking.
Never had soy milk in real life.
It's awful, is it though?
I know people that love it.
Never tried almond milk either, actually.
I'd be blasting ass if I had any dairy.
I love that expression.
Blasting ass.
Chocolate soy milk tastes nice, okay.
I mean, I guess you would have to drink that if you can't have dairy, right?
Well, you go semi-blind Isaac at some point.
Maybe, actually.
Maybe we'll do that.
I don't know yet.
Because it is kind of fun, and it would be cool to get a little further, you know?
We'll see.
I mean, so far, I'm still having fun just discovering new things.
Like today, all the challenges was awesome.
I had a blast with the challenges.
And I had blast with some of the normal runs where I got a good run going.
But then I died of something stupid, and it was just like such a buzzkill, right?
Like, the one where I had technology 5 was such a cool run.
And then it just ended, because I suck, you know?
Do you have a favorite disease?
Probably Crohn's disease.
Just because it's the only one I remember the name of, I don't even know what it is.
I don't know.
I don't have a favorite disease.
What is even Crohn's disease?
I've heard about it, but I don't know what it is.
Yeah, challenges are honestly some of the coolest things.
I thought for sure challenges would be kind of tacky in the beginning of the game when I first started.
Like, I don't know if I would like to play challenges, but now it's actually one of the best.
Intestinal distress disease.
Oh, is that what it is?
Literal shit.
Well, why isn't there an item called Crohn's disease in this game?
That would be fitting, wouldn't it?
That would be so fitting in this game.
Karmic chaos.
We've already done some voting on what characters to play and stuff.
We can keep doing that in the future for sure.
Yeah, that sounds good.
We can do some of that.
A disease that Crohn's you.
Yeah, I don't know, actually.
I guess it would make you poop more.
Maybe every five seconds.
You know the one that goes...
Jim.
You know that one?
But with poop.
So involuntary, you leave poops behind.
Every five seconds.
That could be fun, right?
And if you don't pay attention, the whole map is going to be filled with poop.
I think that would be a fun item.
Who knows?
Maybe it exists already and I just haven't found it.
E.
Coli moment.
Yeah, spawning a poop every 10 seconds.
Something like that, right?
DataMina is interesting.
I don't think I've ever seen that item outside of Greed.
What's up with that?
I feel like I've seen every other Greed run.
That doesn't exist in the normal runs.
We'd love to try that in a normal run.
I did find a train that spawns poop every 30 or 60 seconds.
Did I?
I don't remember that.
I believe you.
Oh, okay.
Maybe it is a coincidence.
I don't think it's a coincidence that I got Kain four times today by random rolling.
I'm telling you, it's not a real random generator that's been coded into this game.
I just don't believe it.
I'm not that unlucky.
Like how many characters are there?
20?
15?
So that's 1 15th times...
You know, how many?
It's crazy.
Kain Fisher playstyle?
You mean vanilla and boring?
Because he's kind of vanilla.
It's the scriptwriter picking for you.
Tell him to switch it up.
Yeah, he's off today, man.
I had to improvise, you know.
Normally, I have a script ready and everything.
Usually, he likes to make it so that I get a couple of shitty runs, you know, and then we end on a banger.
But he wasn't there today.
I mean, I'm not slandering Kain.
I'm just saying he's vanilla.
Vanilla still tastes good.
One of my favorite games of all time is World of Warcraft vanilla.
Okay.
I'm not slandering anything here.
I believe you have 14 unlocked right now.
Okay.
That's still a lot.
So one in 14, you know, and four times you can calculate that.
That's a very small number.
Very low percentage chance.
Okay, it's like artisanal vanilla, high quality.
Yeah, I guess so.
That's a good way to look at it.
Honestly, I don't even see like how he's any different from...
You know what?
I should play Isaac.
The D6, man.
That is... make your own luck, right?
That's what I should be doing.
You got to make my own luck.
Yeah, exactly.
0.00.
Okay, I trust you multiply that right.
You should play Beth.
I hate Beth.
But maybe I'll... Okay, I promise next time we'll do one Beth run, because a lot of people want that.
And then I'll try and figure out how to actually optimize her.
Yeah, you hold me to it.
It's fine, because I'll probably forget.
You will win everything with Beth, right?
We'll see.
Okay, let me ask you guys.
What are your favorite characters in the game?
From the ones I've unlocked, okay?
Which one is your favorite?
Let me see how much of a variation there is.
Eden, Cain, Isaac... Yeah, everyone has different ones, too.
No, Wade, Judas, come on.
Jacob and Esau, Esazel... Okay, everyone has their own favorites.
That probably means the game is pretty balanced, or in terms of fun, right?
Isaac!
Yeah, everyone wants different things.
You know mine, though.
It's my boy, Esazel.
I love Esazel.
Isaac and alternate Esazel.
Oh, alternate Esazel?
I guess alternate Esazel is...
I've only had one or two runs with them, but I will say those were extremely fun.
And I did say that I liked it more than the standard Esazel, but maybe right now it's equal, because I had a bit of recency bias.
So they're pretty much the same for me right now.
Yeah, I gotta play... We gotta play the old Esazel next time, for sure.
I love the short-range attack you do, followed by the very thin long-range.
It's so good.
It's so much fun.
Tainted Esazel rocks.
I really like them, too.
Right?
Why do you call them tainted?
I hope you unlock some more of the old characters.
Some of them are wild.
Yeah, I'm trying.
I'm trying to unlock them.
Allergy strat?
Wait, what is that?
Is that about getting pills or something?
Do a 24-hour stream?
I actually did a 12-hour stream for Undertale once.
That's probably the longest I've streamed.
What would be a good game to do a 24-hour stream on?
Maybe when we start Minecraft season 3, we're gonna do a 24-hour first episode with the mods.
Like, a crazy banger for a first episode.
24 hours, imagine that.
Man, dude, I'm old, you know?
Like, I'm 34 years old.
But I have the body of a 50-year-old.
I don't think I can actually survive that.
I may die.
Even World of Warcraft, I don't think I could play 24 hours.
That is pushing it.
And that's a game I can usually play a lot, you know?
But then, if we did the 24-hour one, we would have to take regular breaks, like, scheduled breaks.
Otherwise, it's gonna be bad.
You sound like a 20-year-old?
Really?
I don't look like it, trust me.
Wait, do you guys think I have a light or a deep voice?
Or somewhere in between?
Because you can never really tell, you know?
By listening to your own voice.
Average in between?
Light?
Nobody is saying deep.
I kind of want a deep voice, though.
I would love to have this David Attenborough-style voice when I get older, you know?
When I become an old fart, that's what I want to sound like.
That's not gonna happen, though.
I will become a Facecam streamer when I hit a million subscribers on YouTube.
Yes.
So spread the word, make people subscribe.
I'm not kidding, I will do it.
Like, permanent Facecam streamer at a million.
I say a million because it'll probably never happen.
And I really do enjoy just not being on Facecam.
But who knows?
I'll never say never, maybe I'll do it at some point.
Even if I don't hit it, you know?
How old are you?
I'm 34.
I have thought about playing Valheim.
I played it briefly with one of my friends in the past.
And we played like an hour and then we both decided, okay, this shit is good.
We're gonna wait until it's actually out of early access, you know?
We wanted to have the full-blown experience, so now I'm waiting for it.
24-hour pool stream.
I don't have a pool, man.
You think I'm rich or something?
You actually watch any other streamers?
I watch...
Yeah, a bunch of different ones, actually.
But of course, now you ask me, I can't think of any.
No, I watch some of Little Indigestion.
I've watched some Apocalypse.
I've watched a guy called Darkness on YouTube.
Julia underscore TV I like to watch sometimes.
I used to watch a lot of Man vs Game, but he's not streaming anymore that much.
If at all, actually.
Day 9 TV, I like to watch him.
I like... let me think.
Who else?
Off the top of my head.
A bunch of Starcraft 2 streamers.
I'm not gonna name them all, but I watch a lot of Starcraft 2.
My favorite YouTuber of all time, not just Starcraft, is Uthermal.
I think I have watched... like, this guy has a lot of videos on his channel.
And I think I have actually watched 90% of them, like, to its completion.
If I go to his page right now, you know all the videos are gonna have this red bar... filled up.
That's my favorite YouTuber of all time.
Like, his content is insane.
It's just so entertaining.
It's crazy.
Love watching him.
Let me think, who else do I watch?
A guy called Three Dog.
He's mainly a...
Metal Gear Solid streamer, but I never watched any Metal Gear Solid from him.
That's what he's known for.
But he also plays, like, weird games.
I saw his playthrough of Death Stranding after I played Death Stranding, and I really loved it.
So that's how I know about him.
I've not played any Metal Gear Solid, but I would love to.
Because I love the Death Stranding, and... you know...
If it's anything like that, Hideo Kojima, you know?
I'm excited.
You are my favorite streamer of all time.
Thank you, Twelve Steps.
Which step are you on?
The red bar disappears after a few months.
Oh, does it?
Okay, then it probably wouldn't show all the red bars.
But you get the idea, right?
Like, I get literally excited every time I get a notification saying that he uploads a new video.
I'm like, fuck, I'm going there right now and I'm gonna watch it.
I'm gonna have some food radio or something, you know?
Favorite game?
Easy.
World of Warcraft Classic.
Me with your icing streams?
Really?
That's awesome.
We all have that one, YouTuber?
I guess so, yeah.
Well, I'm glad you guys are enjoying this.
It's honestly kind of...
What's the word?
I can't find the right word for it.
It's very humbling.
It's very nice.
It means a lot to me that someone would think that...
My stream is worth that much, you know?
That you think, oh man, I gotta drop everything and watch it now.
Because that's crazy.
I'm glad you like it.
I've been binging you while I'm sick from the weather.
That sucks, Nikai.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I've also been suffering a little bit.
Not sickness, but like allergies, but really bad.
I know how you feel.
Is it the pollen or is it just like a cold?
It's been a blast to watch through all the ups and downs.
Yeah.
The game has definitely been a roller coaster, but the ups and downs have been on an upward streak, you know?
Like, we are definitely going up slowly and there may be some dips here and there, just like the stock market right now.
Who knows?
Maybe one day the bubble will collapse and it's gonna be really bad.
It's gonna turn into shit.
I'm gonna have a crazy bad stream where I just die.
Not having fun at all, you know?
I don't know.
Something like that.
It flips 10 to 15 degrees Celsius every day.
Wait, what?
Where are you living?
Where are you living where that happens?
10 to 15 degrees?
That is insane.
Are you in the desert or something?
Are you talking about the night and day or...
Will you play Subnautica?
I've already plated these nuts!
I played the first and below zero.
If you're asking about Subnautica 2...
I'm gonna play it when it's done, man.
It's like saying, how come you're not eating this chili?
Because it's being prepared right now.
The vegetables are being chopped.
It's not even in the pan yet.
Why do you want me to eat this?
You know what I mean?
There's so many people wanting me to play the second one.
No, it's not done.
It's in early access.
I see what you mean, Haruunen.
I also want to play it real bad.
But I know that it's gonna be so much better when it's fully done, you know?
Because everyone that's playing it right now is pretty much just experiencing the worst state of the game it's ever gonna be in.
And they're gonna find all these bugs and all these game-breaking things and all that's gonna be fixed for the future.
Patient gamers, man.
That's the way.
Not only that, you also get to buy it more cheap in the future.
Because there's gonna be sales, right?
Patient gamers is just the way forward.
I don't touch games in early access because I ruined Slay the Spire right now for myself and barely played too.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Oh, you live in India, okay.
10 to 15 degrees change, though.
That's from one day to the next.
Do you decide to play PVC any time?
Are you talking about Protos versus Serg?
You're not, right?
Plants versus zombies.
Is that not a mobile game?
Is it actually good?
Isn't that something on your phone or what?
No, but yes.
Is it a tower defense game?
Because I actually really like the idea behind tower defense games.
I just haven't really played any.
I wish there were some really good tower defense games for PC.
It is tower defense.
Whoa!
Okay!
That sounds fun, then.
It's nostalgic.
I wouldn't say really it's good now.
Well, I've never played it, so maybe it's not good for me now.
It's very easy.
Okay.
Would you ever do stream short playthroughs of smaller games?
Like Mackett or Monke?
I've never heard of those games.
Uh, eggs and beans with toast.
But yes, I would love to do it.
It's just about finding the right games.
And the right time for it.
I usually get very absorbed in one game at a time, or two.
I can't easily jump between, like, a lot of games.
I've not played Myst, but I know what it is.
And I heard it's very difficult.
I had a teacher once that kept talking about it.
Like, he would play it, you know.
Yeah.
They made a remake of it of something recently.
Here's a short game, Persona 5.
Nah, that's not a short game, Tasmak.
Because I've played some of that.
That's a long game.
After, like, 60 hours, they're still giving you tutorials in that game.
That's how long it is.
And which tier would you put it?
Um... Oh, you mean Isaac?
I don't know.
Probably on the same level of Hades.
I think I'm enjoying this as much as I enjoy playing Hades.
Hades won.
I haven't played two yet.
But yeah, those games are kind of comfortable for me, in terms of quality.
And I really loved Hades.
I bet you would hate La Marlana.
Oh yeah, maybe I would love it.
Oh, Blue Baby!
If you want to watch me play horror games, check out the...
Amnesia The Bunker playthrough.
Dude, that is some next-level shit.
I feel like...
I've never been as affected by a game before as that.
That is some crazy shit, okay?
And while you're at it, watch the Chinese Bible in the left ear, chased by World War II monster in the right ear video I made.
Someone who doesn't know what I'm talking about is gonna be so confused right now.
It's a thing, okay?
Just go on the YouTube and Google it, or search for it.
Watching that video will give you an idea of what to expect from that series, okay?
I've played a little bit of XCOM.
I know a little bit of what it is, but I didn't really get too far.
But I wanna play it.
It's also been so long, I don't really remember much anyway.
Like, you could pretty much say it's blind at this point.
It's the same with Red Dead Redemption 2.
When that came out, I watched some review videos, and, you know, I read some articles about it, I saw some streams about it, but I never really got into it.
But I know some things about it, right?
Like, you can have a journal in that game, and it gets filled out and stuff, which I really thought was cool.
But, like, I don't really know much, so it's pretty much still blind, right?
I'm playing Red Dead Redemption 1, actually, right now, and it's amazing.
So I can't wait for Red Dead Redemption 2.
Mod the Bible name to Chinese Bible.
Oh!
Yeah, I could, actually.
That would be kind of fun.
I don't know, Ondoku.
Maybe I will, actually, because right now I am really in it.
Like, I'm really feeling Red Dead Redemption 1.
You know, it depends how I feel right at the end of it.
Maybe I'll throw in a small game beforehand, maybe I'll just jump straight in.
I don't know yet.
But I am definitely excited for Red Dead Redemption 2 playthrough.
I'm recording my voice under a blanket right now for a mockumentary inspired by Kunk on Life.
Are you talking about that British woman?
Because she's hilarious.
I have played the first Amnesia Navi way in the past, way before I started streaming.
It was the first real horror game that I ever completed.
And it is unbelievably terrifying.
So, solid suggestion.
Unfortunately, I've played it already.
But it could be fun to revisit, because...
I don't remember that much about it.
Very, very big spoiler, the game is horses.
Damn, son.
I can't play it now.
I think it would be better straight away, so you won't forget story much.
Yeah, that's a good argument.
That's true.
But like, for stuff like the Talos Principle, for that game, I think I'm actually gonna end up rewatching some of the stuff from my first Let's Play, or at least reading up on the first game again before I start the second.
Because I don't remember everything.
I remember most of it, but there are some grey areas, right?
So I could end up doing that same thing for Red Dead Redemption, depending on what happens.
The background music is called A Woman, from Persona 5.
It's the music that plays during spoiler.
The second area, the museum part.
It's amazing.
That game has incredible music.
Yeah, it's a short game.
Guys, I'm out of here.
Thank you for watching.
Did some good progress unlocking some things today and some challenges.
Not so much on the normal mode.
I'll see you around, okay?
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.